## KAROLINA MALEC

JUNIOR UI/UX DESIGNER

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

Graz Austria

#### PHONE

+43 67764873794

#### **EMAIL**

kara.malec@gmail.com

#### LINKS

Portfolio Website (html & css)

#### SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Figma

• • • 0 0

Adobe Photoshop

• • • • 0

HTML

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

CSS

• • • 0 0

## LANGUAGES

Polish

• • • •

English

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Italian

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

German

• 0 0 0 0

#### HOBBIES

Kitesurfing, Sailing, Snowboarding

#### **PROFILE**

I am a junior Creative User Experience and UI Designer with substantial front end programming skills. In 2022 I decided to shift my career from Architecture to UI UX Design. Architecture is knowing how people interact with their environment, making it similar to UX design career.

My passion is for all forms of digital interface and the interaction it affords between a brand and a customer. I can work with you from conception through delivery or help complete projects you have already started.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### **Architect, Atelier Thomas Pucher**

Graz, Austria

Jan 2022 — Present

## Project Manager, Energotechnika Engineering

Gliwice, Poland

Oct 2020 — Sep 2021

## **Architect, JSK Architekci**

Warsaw, Poland

Jul 2017 — Sep 2020

## **Architect Assistant, Energotechnika Engineering**

Gliwice

Sep 2015 — Jul 2017

### **Architectural practice, KWK Promes**

Katowice, Poland

May 2015 — Sep 2015

## Architectural practice, RARE architecture

London

Jun 2013 — Jun 2014

## EDUCATION

# Masters Degree in Architecture, Silesian University of Technology

Gliwice, Poland

Sep 2011 — May 2017

## Architecture, Univesita di Bologna

Cesena

Jan 2013 — Jan 2014

One year Erasmus programme

#### COURSES

### Freecodecamp course, self-learner